10/13/2016

"I fear nothing. All is, as the Force wills it to be"
is this the legendary donnie yen/future jAsON?!?!?

What I did today:

- Took a quick glance at the research paper. TBH I think we went above and beyond what he was expecting for a draft
so I'm only gonna edit a few minor grammar mistakes. Also, the DCM links look hella boring so hell no.

- Continued working on my own project. Still trying to reach my personal deadline at the end of October before giving
up!!! ;oo

For you:

You are about to find out that Mr. Kosak is serious about doing the seminars. He gives you a little information packet
and everything :/ Signups are on first come first serve basis; would recommend that you get it over with in October
because our project will be pretty grindy. Come November, I wanna start some actual stuff (y)

and as usual, you can do whatever ¯\_(ツ)_/¯

---
throwback: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OD_FxBcwYxs

i was in the hall when jon ko told me to "do the hawk"
somehow this video got leaked by jz and i want 2 kill myself :^)